Hello traders, welcome back to my
channels.  Today in this video we are going to talk
about National Life Insurance Company
who has announced their quarter 4
numbers.  This video is for
educational purpose only.  If you have
not subscribed to the channel then please do
subscribe and if you
want the PDF of the results free of cost
then join the Twitter channel and you will
get the PDF of all the results together and
I will talk about the second point.  So
in the second point, the special point in the Telegram channel is
that you will get to
see a good number of stocks according to the purpose of swing trading.  Where
breakout will be seen.
You will be told about the stocks where a massive jump will be seen.
Those stocks are being told to you free of cost.
Otherwise,
wherever you go, you will
join premium channels there.  If you pay ₹4000 to ₹7000 per month,
you will get to see that stock again.
But you will get to see it here free of cost.
So you must subscribe to that channel.   Let us
discuss the company's quarter four
numbers.  Let us discuss
that, we are seeing the data in rupees in lakhs.
We will talk about
rupees in crores.  So if we talk about the total income of the company, then in the
last quarter three, the
total income of the company has been Rs 15637
crores.  3782 crores.  If we
talk about the last quarter, it has been done
from Rs 2232 crore.
crores. A significant decline is being seen in the
company's total income. The
decline in net income on a quarterly plus yearly basis is being
seen because here,
look here,
what is visible in Income from Investment is a loss of ₹1000 crores.
Due to this, a significant decline is also being seen in the total income of the company. Now
coming to the company's expenses, which are the
expenses of the company, if we are talking about expenses, then in the
last quarter 3, the
company expenses were seen to be 2400
crores, which this time has become 3200 crores. If we are
talking about the previous quarter, then it was
2300 crores, which this time has become 3200
crores. So, according to which a decline is being seen in the company's income,
but an
increase is being seen in the company's expenses. The
expenses of the company are increasing. Then let us
discuss the company's
net profit after settlement.  Let's discuss what we are seeing, if we
talk about the last quarter, then the
net profit of the company is seen to be
385 crores, which has increased to
623 crores this time, if we talk about the last quarter, then it was
387 crores, which has increased to
623 crores this time, quarterly plus yearly,
by the way, a massive jump is being seen,
a good jump is being seen in the net profit of the
company,
friends, the results are being seen quite well on the net profit of the
a good jump is being seen on the quarterly plus yearly basis, now
coming to the
EPS of the company, the EPS of the company is being seen, let's
discuss it, it has become
₹267, ₹41.30 and ₹2.68.
₹4.31, according to which a
jump is being seen in the net profit of the company.  Same
reflection is also seen in 8% of the company.
So friends, the results are
looking quite amazing.  If we
talk about MPA in the results, then MPA is also
seen in good quantity here.
Their MPA is also seen to be blue.
So the results are looking quite good overall.  Then let's
discuss the
company's charts and how they
look.  Let's discuss that.
Talking about charts, from this chart
you will get to see weekly charts.
A trend line is visible in the weekly charts
and you can see the trend line from here.
So the market took support from this trend line.
Then the market is at this
trend line support.  So the
market is seen moving inside this trend line.
But a good move is
not visible here.  The move will be
seen here until the market
sustains above this level.  That horizontal
line that I have made.  Around ₹615.
An entry is possible if a breakout is seen around ₹615.  But a
good entry will be possible only when the
market does
not give a breakout around ₹670,
a good entry will not be possible today and a
good entry will not be possible until the market gives a breakout of this trend line.
Coming to the day
one chart of the company, the market
opened with a good gap up on the day one chart also.  After the gap up opened,
such good selling is also being seen.
But it is looking quite amazing.
Due to this, a
good gap up is seen opening in the market.
Selling is being seen from this and above.
So friends, the overall
trend is seen to be negative.
And unless the market sustains above this,
an entry may not be possible.
I will not say that you should make
entry possible here.  Until the market
crosses above it.  Unless the market
sustains it.  For this reason, I will
not tell you here that
entry is not possible here until the market moves above this.
Safe entry will be possible until the
market crosses around 700 level.
Safe entry will be possible only when a breakout of Rs 700 crore level is seen.
Due to this, safe entry may
not be possible.  And those
who are risky traders can
make an entry here.  But with strict SL I am
not talking about entry current price here or there.  I am not talking about entry at the current price.
I am saying entry.  No
entry is possible until the market breaks out around 615-620.
So friends, I was telling you that you
must join the Telegram channel.
I am talking about Telegram channel
because you will get to see a lot of good stocks here.
Look, I am
posted here today.  4% off Adam Power.
Look here in Adan Power also, I had
told the stock that the breakout of this trend line has come
and it is special.  What is the plus point is
that the breakout of this horizontal line had
not yet come.  So the
breakout of the horizontal line has also happened today and along with it a
good jump of around 4%-7% has been
seen from the trend line,
so it is seen giving a good move.
Talking about the second point, the
second stock I told you about is
MCX, a good breakout is being seen in MCX also.
I am also seeing a breakout of around 7% in MCX.  Let me
tell you.   Let
me show you that a good breakout is being seen in MCX also.
Look at this MCx, I will tell you.
A good breakout is also being seen in MCX.
It is seen coming from above MCX.
And a massive jump is being
seen.  Today MCX is
seen around 400.  So
you can make a good entry.  Entry
Possible I keep giving you many stocks here.
Like there is an Anand Rathi.
I have given this stock also.  Anand Rathi could
not be caught
because Anand
Rathi has given a good rally by giving a breakout.
But if Anand Rathi is
seen doing retest here then
entry here may be possible.  You
can focus on the second point here right now.
You can focus because the
breakout of this TR line is being seen
in power grids.  If a breakout of this horizontal line is
seen then an entry may be
possible here also.  So I have
put a popul here as to
why entry here can be possible.  Why is the reason
put here?  So
you will get to see a stock here
and along with that you will also
get to see news here and along with that you will
also get to see PDF here.  The
PDFs of the results that are coming daily, the
results that I am uploading on the YouTube channels
, you will
get to see their PDFs here free of cost.
That's why I am telling you to
join this telegam channel free of
cost, otherwise somewhere else you will get this telegam
channel at premium, you can
get notifications of these stocks only by paying money there, you
can get these stocks, but here
you are getting to see it free of cost,
so join without delay and
you will get to see all the updates, all the news, all the IPOs
that are coming, what is going on in the market,
you will get to see all of them on the telegram channel,
you will get the links in the comment section.
So friends, if you
like this video, then please do not forget to like, comment and
subscribe.  See you
in the next video with someone new.  Till then
, bye-bye.